{"data":[{"question":"________ thought was given, but all was not approved.","a":"A large number of","b":"A great deal of","c":"Many of","d":"Many","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A great deal of + uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Many\/many of\/ a large number of + countable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Green and magenta are complementary colors located opposite each other on the color wheel, ________.","a":"and blue and yellow so","b":"and too blue and yellow","c":"and so blue and yellow do","d":"and so are blue and yellow","answer":"4","explain":"\n- SO is used to show agreement with positive statements (so\u00a0+ Auxiliary + subject pronoun).\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Double-stars orbit ________.","a":"each to the other","b":"each other","c":"each other one","d":"other each one","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Each other: used to show that each of two or more people does something to the other or others.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"A ________ is a person who searches for valuable minerals.","a":"prospect","b":"prospects","c":"prospector","d":"prospective","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Prospector(n): someone who looks for gold, minerals, oil.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"John F. Kennedy was the youngest president of the United States and ________ to be assassinated.","a":"the fourth","b":"fourth","c":"four","d":"the four","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The fourth: in the place or position counted as number 4","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Oscillatona, one of the few plants that can move about, ________ a wavy, gliding motion.","a":"having","b":"has","c":"being","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When the sentence is separated by a pair of commas in the middle of a sentence, words lie between these two commas are not essential to the meaning of the sentence and they don't affect sentence structure.\u00a0\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Nitrogen must be ________ with another element such as hydrogen or oxygen to be useful in agriculture or industry.","a":"combine","b":"combining","c":"to combine","d":"combined","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice with modal verb (can\/could\/ will, may...): can\/could\/ will\/may...+ be +PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"In ancient times and throughout the middle ages, many people believed that the earth ________ motionless.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tense agreement: When the main clause is in past tense, in the subordinate clause the past tense shows another completed action related in time to the main action.\u00a0\n- Subject (the earth) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Anyone reproducing copyrighted works without permission of the holders of the copyrights ________ breaking the law.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n - Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n+ S: Any one (singular).\u00a0\n+ V: In the blank (...).\u00a0\n+ O: breaking the law.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Supersonic transport ________ the Concorde will probably be widely accepted as soon as problems of noise and atmospheric pollution are resolved.","a":"such","b":"so as","c":"so","d":"such as","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Such as: used when giving an example of something.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}